<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on sreesmere.com</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on sreesmere.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.136.4</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Love for Cosmere</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/love-for-cosmere/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/love-for-cosmere/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a blog at &lt;a href=&#34;https://harshapps.net&#34;&gt;harshapps.net&lt;/a&gt; which is defunct since when my brother stopped paying for it. There were maybe 5 people who visited the site and out of which four engaged in the comments section. If you look at it, it was 80% engagement. But I stopped writing it. Writing a blog like how numerous people have monologued about, it helps me put stuff into a place and into perspective. I started writing this after the election day(Thought I was heading in that direction for this blog but did not - left it for context). Although I have been trying to push to git, on numerous times over the past two years to host a blog. There were numerous iterations, trying out many different jekyll themes and then re-iterating with hugo. Claude + Cursor has definitely sped up this process. Maybe I could have started out how I have been using claude+cursor. Maybe I could have started with writing about the election from my POV, not that anybody cares (Elections always brings so many thoughts. I love it. Again maybe another blog.). But I thought starting out with why I named my all encompassing stuff under sreesmere.com was the way to go.\&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
